^ . ^ . ^ . ^ .COLORED by . ^ . ^ . ^ . ^ ® Sud _ Arun collections ®
( GIRL SINGING EERILY )
( THUNDER RUMBLING )
- ( BELLS JINGLING ) - ( CHILD LAUGHING )
( GIRL CONTINUES SINGING )
( SOFT PIANO MUSIC PLAYING )
Sure I won 't get in trouble , Bill ?
( STUTTERS ) Don 't be a wuss .
I 'd come with you if I weren 't ( COUGHS ) dying .
( SIGHS ) You 're not dying !
( STUTTERING ) You didn 't see the vomit coming out of my nose this morning ?
That 's disgusting .
Okay . Go get the wax .
In the cellar ?
You want it to float , don 't you ?
Fine .
( PIANO CONTINUES PLAYING )
( GROANS )
( DOOR CREAKS )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( FAINT METALLIC CLANGING )
BILL : ( ON
WALKIE-TALKIE ) Georgie .
Hurry up .
( CLICKING SWITCH )
(
WHISPERING ) Okay . I 'm brave .
( SIGHS )
Where 's the wax ?
There 's the wax .
Yes .
( GEORGIE GRUNTS SOFTLY )
- (
CRASHING ) - What was that ? What 's that ?
Oh , jeez .
All right .
There you go .
( STUTTERING ) She 's all ready , Captain .
She ?
You always call boats " she . "
" She . "
Thanks , Billy .
- ( GEORGIE GIGGLES ) - (
CHUCKLES )
See you later . Bye .
Be careful .
( GEORGIE CHUCKLING )
( CONTINUES CHUCKLING )
No !
Oh , Bill 's gonna kill me .
( LOW GROWL )
( YELPS )
Hiya , Georgie .
( BREATHING RAPIDLY )
What a nice boat .
Do you want it back ?
Um , yes , please .
You look like a nice boy . I bet you have a lot of friends .
Three , but my brother 's my best best .
Where is he ?
In bed . Sick .
I bet I can cheer him up . I 'll give him a balloon .
Do you want a balloon too , Georgie ?
I 'm not supposed to take stuff from strangers .
Oh ... Well , I 'm Pennywise the Dancing Clown .
" Pennywise ? " " Yes . " " Meet Georgie .
" Georgie , meet Pennywise . "
( CHUCKLES )
Now we aren 't strangers , are we ?
( WIND CHIMES TINKLING )
What are you doing in the sewer ?
A storm blew me away .
Blew the whole circus away . ( CHUCKLES )
Can you smell the circus , Georgie ?
There 's peanuts , cotton candy ,
hot dogs ,
and ...
Popcorn ?
Popcorn ! ( CHUCKLES ) Is that your favorite ?
- Uh-huh . - Mine , too . ( LAUGHS )
Because they pop . Pop , pop , pop .
( GIGGLES )
Pop , pop , pop .
- Pop . - ( BOTH
LAUGHING )
( LOW GROWLING )
( WHIMPERS ) I should get going now .
Oh .
Without your boat ?
You don 't wanna lose it , Georgie .
Bill 's gonna kill you .
Here .
Take it .
Take it , Georgie .
( GROWLING )
( GEORGIE SCREAMING )
Help !
( CRYING )
( SCREAMS )
Billy ! ( ECHOES )
- ( WIND CHIMES
TINKLING ) - ( CAT MEOWS )
( CHILDREN SINGING INDISTINCTLY )
( SHEEP BLEATING )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
LEROY : Pull it , Mike .
Go on now , pull it .
( MIKE SIGHS )
Here , reload it .
You need to start taking more responsibility around here , Mike .
Your dad was younger than you when he took ...
I 'm not my dad , okay ?
Yeah .
- ( FLIES BUZZING ) - Look at me , son .
Look at me !
There are two places you can be in this world .
You can be out here like us or you can be in there ,
like them .
You waste time hemming and hawing ,
and someone else is gonna make that choice for you .
Except you won 't know it until you feel that bolt between your eyes .
( SHEEP BLEATING )
( SCHOOL BELL RINGS )
So , there 's this church full of Jews , right ?
And Stan has to take this super Jewy test .
But how 's it work ?
They slice the tip of his dick off .
But then Stan will have nothing left !
- That 's true . - Wait up , you guys !
Hey , Stan , what happens at the Bar Mitzvah , anyways ?
Ed says they slice the tip of your ( STUTTERS ) dick off .
Yeah , and I think the rabbi 's gonna pull down your pants ,
turn to the crowd and say , " Where 's the beef ? "
( ALL CHUCKLE )
At the Bar Mitzvah , I read from the Torah ,
and then I make a speech and suddenly , I become a man .
I could think of funner ways to become a man .
- STANLEY : " More fun " you mean . - RICHIE : Oh , shit .
Think they 'll sign my yearbook ?
" Dear Richie , sorry for taking a hot , steaming dump in your backpack last March .
" Have a good summer . "
( KIDS CHATTERING )
- ( GRUNTS ) - ( DOOR BANGS )
GRETTA : Are you in there by yourself , Beaver-ly ?
Or do you have half the guys in the school with you , huh , slut ?
I know you 're in there , little shit . I can smell you .
No wonder you don 't have any friends .
Which is it , Gretta ? Am I a slut or a little shit ?
Make up your mind .
You 're trash .
( GIRLS LAUGHING )
We just wanted to remind you .
GIRL : Such a loser .
( GIRLS CONTINUE LAUGHING )
GRETTA : Well , at least now you 'll smell better .
GIRL : Gross .
Let 's go , girls .
Have a nice summer , Beaver-ly .
- GIRL : Pathetic . - ( SIGHS )
( KIDS CHATTERING )
Best feeling ever .
Yeah ?
Try tickling your pickle for the first time .
Hey , what do you guys wanna do tomorrow ?
I start my training .
- EDDIE : Wait , what training ? - Street Fighter .
Is that how you wanna spend your summer ? Inside of an arcade ?
Beats spending it inside of your mother .
- Oh ! - What if we go to the quarry ?
Guys , we have the ( STUTTERS ) Barrens .
Right .
Betty Ripsom 's mom .
STANLEY : Is she really expecting to see her come out of that school ?
EDDIE : I don 't know .
As if Betty Ripsom 's been hiding in Home Ec. for the last few weeks .
STANLEY : You think they 'll actually find her ?
RICHIE : Sure .
In a ditch . All decomposed , covered in worms and maggots .
Smelling like Eddie 's mom 's underwear .
Shut up ! That 's freaking disgusting .
She 's not dead . ( STUTTERS ) She 's missing .
Sorry , Bill . She 's missing .
You know the Barrens aren 't that bad .
Who doesn 't love splashing around in shitty water ?
( BOTH GRUNTING )
Nice Frisbee , flamer .
- Give it back ! - ( LAUGHS )
PATRICK : Fucking losers !
( BURPS )
HENRY : Loser .
( STUTTERS ) You suck , Bowers .
EDDIE : Shut up , Bill .
(
STUTTERS
MOCKINGLY ) You say something , Billy ?
You got a free ride this year ' cause of your little brother .
Ride 's over , Denbrough .
( INDISTINCT POLICE RADIO CHATTER )
This summer 's gonna be a hurt train for you and your faggot friends .
( PATRICK LAUGHING )
I wish he 'd go missing .
He 's probably the one doing it .
( CAR ENGINE REVS )
You gonna let me go by ?
Or is there a secret password or something ?
BEN : Oh .
- Um , sorry . - Sorry isn 't ...
(
CLATTERING )
A password .
( CLATTERING )
Henry and his goons are over by the west entrance .
So you should be fine .
Oh , I wasn 't ...
Everyone knows he 's looking for you .
( SIGHS )
What you listening to ?
( POP MUSIC PLAYING ON HEADPHONES )
New Kids on the Block .
I don 't even like them . I was just ...
Wait . You 're the new kid , right ? Now I get it .
There 's nothing to get .
I 'm just messing with you .
I 'm Beverly Marsh .
Yeah . I know that ' cause we 're in the same class .
Social Studies . And you were ...
I 'm Ben . But pretty much everybody just calls me ...
The new kid .
Well , Ben , there are worse things to be called .
Let me sign this .
Stay cool , Ben from sosh class .
Uh , yeah .
You too , Beverly .
BEVERLY : Hang tough , new kid on the block .
( CHUCKLES )
" Please Don 't Go , Girl . "
That 's the name of another New Kids on the Block song .
( POP MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING ON HEADPHONES )
BILL : (
STUTTERING ) " He thrusts his fists against the posts ...
" He thrusts his fists against ...
(
CONTINUES
STUTTERING ) Shit !
" Post . "
Need some help ? I ... ( STUTTERS )
I thought we agreed .
- Before you say anything ... - Bill .
Just let me show you something first .
( WATER FLOW STOPS )
The Barrens .
( STUTTERING ) It 's the only place that Georgie could have ended up .
He 's gone , Bill .
But if the storm swept Georgie in , we should have gone ...
He 's gone ! He 's dead !
He 's dead ! There is nothing we can do ! Nothing !
Now take this down before your mother sees it .
Next time you wanna take something from my office ...
Ask .
I guess you get your tunnels back .
( SQUEAKING )
HENRY : Get in !
WOMAN : Creep !
( PANTING )
MIKE : Oh , Jesus .
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( SIGHS )
- ( SOFT GROWL ) - ( CHAIN
RATTLING )
( CHAIN CLINKS )
WOMAN : Mike ! ( SCREAMS )
( WOMAN CONTINUES SCREAMING )
MAN : Hurry , son !
WOMAN : Help ! It burns !
MAN : Mike !
( WOMAN CONTINUES SCREAMING )
( METALLIC CLANKING )
( DISTORTED GRUNTING )
( SHEEP BLEATING )
( BREATHING SHAKILY )
( TIRES SCREECH )
( MIKE GRUNTS )
( ROCK MUSIC BLASTING ON CAR STEREO )
Stay the fuck outta my town !
- ( TIRES SQUEAL ) - (
BREATHING SHAKILY )
- ( CHAIN RATTLES ) - ( GASPS )
Mike ?
- Are you okay ? - (
CONTINUES
BREATHING SHAKILY )
( STANLEY RECITING IN HEBREW )
( CONTINUES RECITING IN HEBREW )
( RABBI URIS CONTINUES IN HEBREW )
You 're not studying , Stanley .
How 's it going to look ?
The rabbi 's son can 't finish his own Torah reading .
Take the book to my office .
Obviously you 're not using it .
( EXHALES )
( CLATTERING )
( LIGHT BUZZING )
( BREATHES SHAKILY )
( BREATHING RAGGEDLY )
( DOOR CREAKING )
( GASPS )
( BREATH TREMBLING )
( METALLIC CLATTERING )
( GASPING )
( DISTORTED VOICES CHATTERING )
( LOW GROWL )
( SCREAMING )
EDDIE : Take everything but the Delicious Deals , guys .
My mom loves them .
Hey ! First you said the Barrens , and now you 're saying the sewer .
I mean , what if we get caught ?
BILL : We won 't , Eds . ( STUTTERS ) The sewers are public works .
We 're the public , aren 't we ?
Hey , Eddie , these your birth control pills ?
Yeah , and I 'm saving it for your sister . This is private stuff .
HOSTESS : ( ON TV ) Hello , and welcome to the Derry Children 's Hour .
Eddie Bear , where you boys off to in such a rush ?
Um ... (
STAMMERS )
( STUTTERS ) Just my backyard , Mrs. K.
I got a new ...
A new croquet set . Jeez , spit it out , ( MOCK STUTTERS ) Bill !
Okay .
Oh , and sweetie , don 't go rolling around on the grass .
Especially if it 's just been cut .
You know how bad your allergies can get .
Yes , Mom . Let 's go .
MRS. KASPBRAK : Aren 't you forgetting something ?
HOSTESS : Water is all around us . It 's even above us .
( EDDIE SIGHS )
Don 't believe me ?
Then try it yourself at home .
- ( RICHIE
CHUCKLES ) - Whenever you 're outside ...
Do you want one from me too , Mrs. K ?
- I was kidding . - EDDIE : No , no , no .
Sorry , Mommy .
" Your hair is winter fire , January embers ...
" My heart burns there too . "
RICHIE : Slow down !
BILL : Hi-ho , Silver !
Away !
RICHIE : Your old lady bike 's too fast for us !
LIBRARIAN : Found it .
Isn 't it summer vacation ?
I would think you 'd be ready to take a break from the books .
I like it in here .
A boy should be spending his summer outside with friends .
Don 't you have any friends ?
Can I have the book now ?
( PANTING )
( GIRL GIGGLES )
( MUSIC BOX PLAYING )
( MUSIC STOPS )
( SIZZLING )
( ELECTRICITY CRACKLES )
( GIRL GIGGLING )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( GIGGLING CONTINUES )
( CLATTERING )
( PANTING )
PENNYWISE : Egg boy .
- ( GRUNTS ) - ( GASPS )
LIBRARIAN : What on earth are you doing ?
( PANTING )
Where are you off to , tits ?
Gotcha .
- BEN : Wait . - ( BOYS
CHATTERING )
- HENRY : Fucking hold him . - BEN : Leave me alone !
- PATRICK : Smack him . - HENRY : Don 't let tubby get away .
BEN : Help !
HENRY : Get him ! ( LAUGHS )
- Hold him , Hockstetter . - VICTOR : Get him , Belch .
( EXCLAIMING )
BEN : Stop !
- Just leave me alone . - Look at all this blubber !
Let me light his hair , like Michael Jackson .
HENRY : Just hold him .
Get off me ! Get off me !
( CAR APPROACHING )
Help !
( BEN GRUNTING )
- ( EARS RINGING ) - ( MUFFLED YELLING )
Okay , new kid .
This is what us locals call the Kissing Bridge .
It 's famous for two things . Sucking face ,
(
CHUCKLES )
and carving names .
Henry , please .
- ( SCREAMS ) - ( BULLIES
LAUGHING )
Whoa , whoa ! Henry !
Shut up !
I 'm gonna carve my whole name onto this cottage cheese !
( GRUNTING )
I 'm gonna cut your fucking tits off . I swear to God !
Get him !
Come on !
( GRUNTING )
Get him !
You can 't run !
( BULLIES LAUGHING )
- Oh , no ! - HENRY : We need to find Fatty !
( GRUNTING )
My knife . My old man will kill me !
- You two , get him ! - PATRICK : Come on !
Move your fucking ass !
PATRICK : He 's going that way ! Come on !
( PANTING )
He 's down there .
EDDIE : I don 't know . I guess .
That 's poison ivy . And that 's poison ivy .
And that 's poison ivy .
Where ? Where 's the poison ivy ?
Nowhere . Not every fucking plant is poison ivy , Stanley .
EDDIE : Okay , I 'm starting to get itchy now
and I 'm pretty sure this is not good for my ...
RICHIE : Do you use the same bathroom as your mother ?
- EDDIE : Sometimes , yeah . - RICHIE : Then you probably have crabs .
EDDIE : That 's so not funny .
Aren 't you guys coming in ?
Uh-uh . It 's greywater .
What the hell 's greywater ?
It 's basically piss and shit . So I 'm just telling you ,
you guys are splashing around in millions of gallons of Derry pee . So ...
Are you serious ? What are you ...
( IN SPANISH ACCENT ) Doesn 't smell like caca to me , señor .
Okay , I can smell that from here .
It 's probably just your breath wafting back into your face .
( SCOFFS ) Have you ever heard of a staph infection ?
Oh , I 'll show you a staff infection .
EDDIE : This is so unsanitary . You 're literally ...
This is literally like swimming inside of a toilet bowl right now .
Have you ever heard of Listeria ?
( SCREAMS )
( STAMMERS ) Are you retarded ?
You 're the reason why we 're in this position right now .
BILL : Guys !
Shit . Don 't tell me that 's ...
BILL : No .
( STUTTERS ) Georgie wore galoshes .
EDDIE : Whose sneaker is it ?
It 's Betty Ripsom 's .
Oh , shit .
Oh , God . Oh , fuck !
I don 't like this .
How do you think Betty feels ?
Running around these tunnels with only one frickin ' shoe ?
( RICHIE CHUCKLES )
What if she 's still here ?
Eddie , come on !
My mom will have an aneurysm , if she finds out that we 're playing down here .
I 'm serious .
Bill ?
If ... If I was Betty Ripsom , I would want us to find me .
( STUTTERS ) Georgie too .
What if I don 't want to find them ?
I mean , no offense , Bill , but I don 't want to end up like ...
I don 't want to go missing either .
- He has a point . - (
STUTTERS ) You too ?
It 's summer .
We 're supposed to be having fun .
This isn 't fun .
This is scary and disgusting .
- ( GRUNTS ) - ( GASPS )
( GRUNTING )
Holy shit ! What happened to you ?
( CLATTERING )
( SPRAY CAN RATTLING )
( DISTANT CLATTERING )
( LIGHTER CLICKS )
I hear ya , tits .
Don 't think you can stay down here all damn day now .
VOICE : ( WHISPERING ) You found us , Patrick .
( VOICES WHISPERING ) You found us , Patrick .
- ( GASPS ) - Patrick .
- (
SCREAMING ) - (
DISTORTED CHATTER )
( GIRL LAUGHS )
( GROANS )
( GASPING )
( PANTING )
Fuck !
( GIRL LAUGHING )
( CHILDREN SINGING )
- (
SCREAMING ) - ( YELLING )
EDDIE : I think it 's great that we 're helping the new kid ,
but also we need to think of our own safety .
I mean , he 's bleeding all over and you guys know
that there 's an AIDS epidemic happening right now as we speak , right ?
My mom 's friend in New York City got it by touching a dirty pole on the subway .
And a drop of AIDS blood got into his system through a hangnail . A hangnail !
And you can amputate legs and arms .
But how do you amputate a waist ?
You guys do know that alleys are known for dirty needles that have AIDS , right ?
You guys do know that ?
- Hey ... - Ah , we 're screwed .
Richie , wait here . Come on .
Glad I got to meet you before you died .
Okay .
BILL : Can we afford all that ?
It 's all we got .
You kidding me ?
Wait , you have an account here , don 't you ?
If my mom finds out I bought all this stuff for myself ...
I 'm spending the whole rest of the weekend in the emergency room getting X-rayed .
( MUSIC PLAYING FAINTLY ON SPEAKERS )
- GRETTA : See you later , Dad . - KEENE : See you , Gretta .
BILL : You okay ?
I 'm fine . What 's wrong with you ?
None of your business .
There 's a kid outside . Looked like someone killed him .
( STUTTERS ) We need some supplies ,
but we don 't have enough money .
( INDISTINCT CHATTERING )
I like your glasses , Mr. Keene .
You look just like Clark Kent .
Oh . (
LAUGHING )
I don 't know about that .
Can I try them ?
Mmm . Sure .
( BEVERLY CHUCKLES SOFTLY )
What do you think ?
Well , how about that ?
You look just like Lois Lane .
(
CHUCKLES ) Really ?
Mmm .
Well , here you go .
( CLATTERING )
Shoot , I 'm so sorry .
It 's okay .
( EDDIE GRUNTS )
( DOORBELL JINGLES )
RICHIE : Just suck the wound .
- EDDIE : I need to focus right now . - RICHIE : You need to focus ?
EDDIE : Yeah , can you go get me something ?
- Jesus ! What do you need ? - Go get my bifocals .
I hid ' em in my second fanny pack .
STANLEY : Why do you have two fanny packs ?
EDDIE : I need to focus right now and it 's a long story .
I don 't want to get into it .
BILL : (
STUTTERS ) Um , thanks .
Even-steven .
STANLEY : Oh , God , he 's bleeding . Oh , my God !
Ben from sosh ?
RICHIE : You have to suck the wound before you apply the Band-Aids .
- This is 101 . - You don 't know what you 're talking about .
Are you okay ? That looks like it hurts .
Oh . No , I 'm good . I just fell .
Yeah , right into Henry Bowers .
(
STUTTERING ) Shut it , Richie .
Why ? It 's the truth .
You sure they got the right stuff to fix you up ?
You know , we 'll take care of him .
Uh , thanks again , Beverly .
Sure . Maybe I 'll see you around .
(
CONTINUES
STUTTERING ) Yeah , we were thinking about going to the quarry tomorrow ,
if you wanna
come .
Good to know . Thanks .
Nice going bringing up Bowers in front of her .
Yeah , dude , you heard what she did .
What 'd she do ?
More like " Who 'd she do ? "
From what I hear , the list is longer than my wang .
That 's not saying much .
( STUTTERS ) They 're just rumors .
Anyway , Bill had her back in third grade .
They kissed in the school play .
The reviews said you can 't fake that sort of passion .
( IN BRITISH ACCENT ) Now , pip-pip and tally-ho , my good fellows ,
I do believe this chap requires our utmost attention .
Get in there , Dr. K. Come on , fix him up .
Why don 't you shut the fuck up , Einstein , because I know what I 'm doing
and I don 't want you doing the British guy with me right now .
( IN BRITISH ACCENT ) Suck the wound . Get in there .
HOSTESS : ( ON TV ) Toilet and bath water travel down
- the drains and into the sewer . - ( DOOR OPENS )
The sewer is a fun place to play with all of your friends .
Just follow the water into the drains and down into the sewers you go .
When you 're with your friends in the sewers , you can be as silly as a clown !
That 's right , it 's the word of the day .
Hi , Daddy .
Hey , Bevvie .
Whatcha got there ?
Just some things .
Like what ?
( PLASTIC RUSTLES )
( SNIFFING )
Tell me you 're still my little girl .
Yes , Daddy .
Good .
ANNOUNCER : ( ON TV ) A deep fly ball to the left . His last at bat .
He scratched the foul pole .
Wade Boggs , of course , leads the league in hitting so far .
( BEVERLY SOBBING )
( FAUCET SPUTTERING )
( SNIFFLES )
This is what you did . This is what you ... ( GRUNTS )
This is ...
( CONTINUES SOBBING )
( BOYS CLEARING THROATS )
EDDIE : Lay it out .
( CHUCKLES )
Oh , my God .
- So easy . - Poor tree .
So easy !
Oh , my God , that was terrible . I win .
- You won ? - Yeah .
- Did you see my loogie ? - That went the farthest !
- It 's by distance . - Mass . It 's always been mass .
( STAMMERS ) What is mass ?
Who cares how far it goes ?
It matters how cool it looks , like it 's green or it 's white or juicy and fat .
- All right . - Thanks for that .
- Who 's first ? - That was terrible .
BEVERLY : I 'll go !
Sissies .
RICHIE : What the fuck !
Oh , holy shit ! We just got showed up by a girl .
Do we have to do that now ?
Yes .
BEVERLY : Come on !
Oh , shit .
( WHOOPING )
( INDISTINCT CHATTERING )
RICHIE : I already won ! We already won !
( ALL LAUGHING )
They 're down ! Yes !
( EXCLAIMING )
( INDISTINCT CHATTERING )
RICHIE : Ah , fuck ! What was that ?
STANLEY : Something just touched my foot right here .
That work ?
- Where are we looking ? - Right here , right here !
It 's a turtle .
( UPBEAT RAP MUSIC PLAYING ON CASSETTE PLAYER )
- ( ALL GASP ) - ( BOYS CLEAR
THROATS )
News flash , Ben . School 's out for summa !
Oh , that ? That 's not school stuff .
- RICHIE : Who sent you this ? - BEN : No one . Give it ...
No one .
- RICHIE : What 's with the history project ? - BEN : Oh ...
When I first moved here , I didn 't have anyone to hang out with ,
so I just started spending time in the library .
RICHIE : You went to the library ?
On purpose ?
BEVERLY : Oh , I wanna see .
STANLEY : What 's The Black Spot ?
EDDIE : The Black Spot was a nightclub
that was burned down years ago by that racist cult .
STANLEY : The what ?
EDDIE : Don 't you watch Geraldo ?
(
STUTTERS ) Your hair ...
Your ... Your hair is beautiful , Beverly .
Oh .
Right . Thanks .
RICHIE : Here , pass it .
Why is it all murders and missing kids ?
Derry 's not like any town I 've ever been in before .
They did a study once , and it turns out
people die or disappear six times the national average .
You read that ?
BEN : And that 's just grown-ups .
Kids are worse .
Way , way worse .
I 've got more stuff if you wanna see it .
( SOFTLY ) No , no .
( PANTING )
EDDIE : Don 't freak out , just tell us .
RICHIE : Yeah . I heard he has a rollercoaster and a pet chimp
and an old guy 's fucking bones . Yeah .
Whoa , whoa , whoa .
Wow .
Cool , huh ?
No . No , nothing cool .
There 's nothing cool .
This is cool , right here . Wait , no . No , it 's not cool .
What 's that ?
Oh , that ? That 's the charter for Derry Township .
Nerd alert .
No , actually , it 's really interesting .
Derry started as a beaver trapping camp .
Still is , am I right , boys ?
Ninety-one people signed the charter that made Derry .
But later that winter , they all disappeared without a trace .
The entire camp ?
BEN : There were rumors of Indians , but no sign of an attack .
Everybody just thought it was a plague or something .
But it 's like
one day everybody just woke up and left .
The only clue was a trail of bloody clothes leading to the well house .
RICHIE : Jesus . We can get Derry on Unsolved Mysteries .
( DOOR CREAKING )
- EDDIE : Let 's do that . You 're brilliant . - RICHIE : I might be .
( BOYS CHATTERING )
RICHIE : I don 't know .
Maybe he 's just trying to make some friends , Stanley .
Where was the well house ?
I don 't know . Somewhere in town , I guess .
Why ?
Nothing .
( CHOIR SINGING SPIRITUAL SONG ) Nobody knows the trouble I 've seen
Nobody knows my sorrow
( EDDIE PLAYING HAND FLUTE )
( WATCH BEEPING )
( DOOR CREAKING )
( GROWLING )
HOARSE MALE VOICE : Eddie ...
What are you looking for ?
- ( PILLBOX RATTLES ) - Oh !
( SOFTLY ) Fuck . My mom 's gonna fucking flip .
( EDDIE MUMBLING INDISTINCTLY )
Do you think this will help me , Eddie ?
( GROWLING AND MUMBLING INDISTINCTLY )
- ( GASPS ) - (
GROWLING )
( EDDIE WHIMPERING )
( CONTINUES GROWLING )
Help ! Help !
( ROARING )
( EDDIE SCREAMING )
( PANTING )
Where you going , Eds ?
If you lived here , you 'd be home by now .
Come join the clown , Eds .
You 'll float down here .
We all float down here .
Yes , we do .
( LAUGHING )
( SCREAMING )
( DISTORTED LAUGHTER )
( BALLOONS POPPING )
( LOCK CLICKS )
BEVERLY : (
WHISPERING ) " Your hair is winter fire ...
" January embers ...
" My heart burns there , too . "
GIRL : Beverly ...
( WATER DRIPPING )
Beverly .
Help me .
Help me , please .
VOICES : ( ECHOING ) We all want to meet you , Beverly .
We all float down here .
BEVERLY : Hello ? Who are you ?
-
VERONICA : I 'm Veronica . - BETTY : Betty Ripsom .
PATRICK : Patrick Hockstetter .
VERONICA : Come closer .
- BETTY : Wanna see ? -
VERONICA : We float .
PATRICK : (
HOARSELY ) We change .
( DISTORTED GIGGLING )
- ( TAPE RATTLES ) - ( GIRL
GIGGLING )
( SIGHS )
( SCREAMS )
( WHIMPERS )
( GRUNTS )
( SCREAMING )
Daddy !
Help !
( SCREAMING )
( GASPS )
( WHIMPERING )
( SOBBING )
( SOBBING AND SCREAMING )
The hell 's going on ?
(
STUTTERING SHAKILY ) The sink ...
CONTINUES
STUTTERING )
And the blood ... It 's ...
What blood ?
The sink . You don 't see it ? ( STAMMERING )
There was blood .
( STAMMERING )
( MUMBLES SHAKILY )
You worry me , Bevvie .
You worry me a lot .
( SOFTLY ) But don 't you see ?
Why 'd you do this to your hair ?
Makes you look like a boy .
( SOBBING )
( THUNDER RUMBLING )
( SWITCH CLICKS )
( PUTS DOWN BUCKET )
( SOBBING SOFTLY )
( FOOTSTEPS RUNNING )
( GASPS )
( SOFTLY ) Georgie .
( BREATH TREMBLING )
( STAIRS CREAKING )
GEORGIE : I lost it , Billy . Don 't be mad .
( STUTTERS ) I 'm not mad at you .
GEORGIE : It just floated off .
But , Bill , if you 'll come with me ,
you 'll float , too .
Georgie .
You 'll float , too . ( CHUCKLING ) You 'll float , too .
You 'll float , too .
You 'll float , too . ( IN HARSH VOICE ) You 'll float , too .
You 'll float , too . You 'll float , too .
You 'll float , too .
( DISTORTED ) You 'll float , too ! You 'll float , too !
You 'll float , too !
( ROARING )
STANLEY : No , we gotta go through the alleyway .
- EDDIE : The alley takes way too long . - STANLEY : No , the alley is so much faster .
EDDIE : The alley is more dangerous and it 's disgusting .
- STANLEY : How is it more dangerous ? - EDDIE : It smells like piss and it 's gross .
- Just take the side streets for once . -
STANLEY : Oh , my God .
The side streets are the same . They smell like piss and shit .
EDDIE : Okay , okay . Can you just tell me what she said exactly ?
STANLEY : She didn 't say anything .
She just said that you guys need to hurry over .
EDDIE : She didn 't say anything . Okay . Okay .
BEVERLY : You made it . I ...
I need to show you something .
What is it ?
More than we saw at the quarry ?
Shut up ! Just shut up , Richie .
My dad will kill me if he finds out I had boys in the apartment .
Then we 'll leave a lookout .
( STUTTERS ) Richie , stay here .
Whoa , whoa , whoa ! What if her dad comes back ?
Do what you always do . Start talking .
It is a gift .
In there .
STANLEY : What is it ?
BEVERLY : You 'll see .
EDDIE : Are you taking us to your bathroom ?
I just want you to know that 89 % of the worst accidents in homes
are caused in bathrooms . ( STUTTERING )
And , I mean , that 's where all the bacteria and fungi are
and it 's not a really sanitary place ... ( MUMBLES )
- ( DOOR
CREAKING OPEN ) - ( EDDIE
WHIMPERING )
I knew it ! ( GAGS )
BEVERLY : You see it ?
- EDDIE : Yes . -
STANLEY : What ...
What happened in here ?
My dad couldn 't see it . I thought I might be crazy .
BEN : Well , if you 're crazy , then we 're all crazy .
( STUTTERS ) We can 't leave it like this .
( ROCK MUSIC PLAYING )
( EXCLAIMS )
- (
BEVERLY
CHUCKLES ) - BILL : All right , so you 've
never been to the Derry Summer Fair ?
- No , I don 't think so . - ( BOTH
CHUCKLE )
Not that I know of .
BILL : Well , I go there every year ,
but I was there one time with Richie and technically won ' cause I hit the target .
But there were so many prizes , I didn 't know which to pick .
It 's not true , you know .
What they say about me .
I was only ever kissed by one guy .
It was a long time ago .
It was a nice kiss though .
" January embers . "
( STUTTERING ) Was that in the play ?
No , the poem .
Oh ... (
CHUCKLES )
(
STUTTERING ) Oh , I don 't really know much poetry .
Oh . I was just ...
Never mind then .
Um ...
Just so you know , I ...
I never believed any of the rumors .
( STUTTERING ) And none of us Losers do .
We like hanging with you .
Thanks .
You shouldn 't thank us too much .
Hanging out with us makes you a Loser , too .
( LAUGHS )
I can take that .
( BOTH CHUCKLE )
RICHIE : No , I love being your personal doorman , really .
Could you idiots have taken any longer ?
- EDDIE : All right , shut up , Richie . - STANLEY : Yeah , shut up , Richie .
Oh , okay , trash the trashmouth , I get it .
Hey , I wasn 't the one scrubbing the bathroom floor
and imagining that her sink went all Eddie 's mom 's vagina on Halloween .
She didn 't imagine it .
I ...
( STUTTERS ) I saw something , too .
STANLEY : You saw blood , too ?
Not blood .
( STUTTERS ) I saw Georgie .
It seemed so real .
I mean , it seemed like him , but there was this ...
The clown .
Yeah , I saw him , too .
Wait , can only virgins see this stuff ?
Is that why I 'm not seeing this shit ?
( INDISTINCT CHATTERING IN DISTANCE )
EDDIE : Oh , shit , that 's Belch Huggins ' car .
- We should probably get outta here . - RICHIE : Yeah .
Wait , isn 't that the homeschooled kid 's bike ?
EDDIE : Yeah , that 's Mike 's .
We have to help him .
RICHIE : We should ?
Yes .
- HENRY : Come on . - (
STRAINING )
Eat that meat !
- Eat it , bitch ! - You little fucker !
- Bitch ! - Motherfucker !
- BELCH : Eat it , you little bitch ! - VICTOR : Pussy !
BELCH : Fucking ...
Whatcha gonna do , huh ?
Get up !
Get the fuck up !
( LAUGHS )
VICTOR : You little fucker !
( YELLS )
( PANTING )
( GROANING )
Come on , Henry , smack him !
- ( HENRY GRUNTS ) - You little bitch .
- Nice throw . - Thanks .
HENRY : You losers are trying too hard .
She 'll do you .
You just gotta ask nicely ,
- like I did . - ( LAUGHS )
( YELLS )
( GRUNTS )
What the fuck ?
( GRUNTING )
HENRY : Come on , get ' em ! Fuck !
Rock war ! ( GRUNTS )
( ALL GRUNTING )
- HENRY : Get ' em ! -
STANLEY : Watch out !
RICHIE : Fuck you , motherfuckers !
BILL : Eddie !
- RICHIE : Fuck outta here ! - Ow !
Ah , shit !
Fuck you , bitch !
EDDIE : Come on , guys ! Let 's get ' em !
- VICTOR : Fuck this . - BELCH : Fuck out of here .
VICTOR : Fuck you , losers !
( PANTING )
Go blow your dad , you mullet-wearing asshole !
Thanks , guys , but you shouldn 't have done that .
They 'll be after you guys , too , now .
Oh , no , no , no . Bowers ? He 's always after us .
( STUTTERS ) I guess that 's one thing we all have in common .
Yeah , Homeschool . Welcome to the Losers ' Club .
( EXCITED CHATTER )
WOMAN : Right there .
( PLAYING TUBA )
STANLEY : They say they found part of his hand all chewed up near the Standpipe .
He asked to borrow a pencil once .
( STUTTERS ) It 's like she 's been forgotten because Corcoran 's missing .
( RICHIE CONTINUES PLAYING TUBA )
Is it ever gonna end ?
RICHIE : What the fuck , dude ?
What are you guys talking about ?
What they always talk about .
I actually think it will end .
For a little while , at least .
What do you mean ?
So I was going over all my Derry research and I charted out all the big events .
The Ironworks explosion in 1908 ,
the Bradley Gang in ' 35 ,
and The Black Spot in ' 62 .
And now kids being ...
I realized this stuff seems to happen ...
BOTH : Every 27 years .
EDDIE : Okay , so , let me get this straight .
It comes out from wherever to eat kids for , like , a year ?
And then what ? It just goes into hibernation ?
Maybe it 's like ... What do you call it ?
Cicadas .
You know , the bugs that come out once every 17 years .
My grandfather thinks this town is cursed .
He says that all the bad things that happen in this town are because of one thing .
An evil thing that feeds off the people of Derry .
But it can 't be one thing .
We all saw something different .
MIKE : Maybe .
Or maybe It knows what scares us most and that 's what we see .
( STUTTERS ) I saw a leper .
He was like a walking infection .
But you didn 't .
Because it isn 't real .
None of this is .
Not Eddie 's leper
( STUTTERING ) or Bill seeing Georgie
or the woman I keep seeing .
She hot ?
No , Richie .
She 's not hot .
Her face is all messed up .
None of this makes any sense .
They 're all like bad dreams .
I don 't think so . I know the difference between a bad dream and real life , okay ?
What 'd you see ? You saw something , too ?
MIKE : Yes .
Do you guys know that burned-down house on Harris Avenue ?
I was inside when it burned down .
Before I was rescued , my mom and dad were trapped in the next room over from me .
They were pushing and pounding on the door ,
( WOMAN
SCREAMING
FAINTLY )
trying to get to me .
MAN : Hurry , son !
WOMAN : It burns !
But it was too hot .
( WOMAN SCREAMS )
When the firemen finally found them ,
the skin on their hands had melted down to the bone .
We 're all afraid of something .
- (
CRACKER
WHIZZES ) - Got that right .
EDDIE : Why , Rich ? What are you afraid of ?
( CRACKERS BURSTING )
Clowns .
BILL : Okay .
Look .
( STUTTERS ) That 's where Georgie disappeared .
There 's the Ironworks .
And The Black Spot .
Everywhere it happens , it 's all connected by the sewers .
And they all meet up at the ...
The well house .
It 's in the house on Neibolt Street .
You mean that creepy-ass house where all the junkies and hobos like to sleep ?
- (
GASPING ) - BEVERLY : I hate that place .
It always feels like it 's watching me .
EDDIE : That 's where I saw It .
That 's where I saw the clown .
( STUTTERS ) That 's where It lives .
( INHALES SHARPLY )
STANLEY : I can 't imagine anything ever wanting to live there .
EDDIE : Can we stop talking about this ?
( STUTTERING ) I can barely breathe .
This is summer .
We 're kids . I can barely breathe .
I 'm up here having a fucking asthma attack .
( GASPS ) I 'm not doing this .
What the hell ? Put the map back .
Mmm-mmm .
( PROJECTOR CLICKING )
What happened ?
STANLEY : What 's going on ?
MIKE : I got it . Hold on .
Guys .
BILL : Georgie .
STANLEY : Bill ?
( PROJECTOR CLICKING RAPIDLY )
( ALL GASPING )
RICHIE : What the fuck ?
BILL : It 's It !
What the fuck is that ? What the fuck is that ?
I don 't fucking know !
( ALL WHIMPERING )
Turn it off ! Turn it off !
RICHIE : Yeah . Yeah , turn it off . Turn it off !
( ALL PANTING )
- ( GROWLS ) - ( ALL SCREAM )
- ( LAUGHS ) - RICHIE : Run , Stanley !
( ALL SCREAMING )
EDDIE : What is it ?
RICHIE : What the fuck ?
( ALL SCREAMING )
( ALL PANTING )
Thanks , Ben .
EDDIE : It saw us .
It saw us , and it knows where we are .
It always did .
So , let 's go .
BEN : Go ?
Go where ?
Neibolt .
( STUTTERS ) That 's where Georgie is .
After that ?
Yeah , it 's summer . We should be outside .
If you say it 's summer one more fucking time ...
BEVERLY : Bill !
Wait !
( STUTTERS ) " He thrusts his fists
" against the posts
" and still insists he sees ... "
BEVERLY : Bill !
Bill , you can 't go in there .
This is crazy .
Look , you don 't have to come in with me .
But what happens when another Georgie goes missing ?
Or another Betty ? Or another Ed Corcoran ? Or one of us ?
Are you just gonna pretend it isn 't happening like everyone else in this town ?
Because I can 't .
I go home , and all I see is that Georgie isn 't there .
His clothes , his toys , his stupid stuffed animals , but ...
He isn 't .
So walking into this house ,
for me ,
it 's easier than walking into my own .
RICHIE : Wow .
BEN : What ?
He didn 't stutter once .
Wait !
Um ...
Shouldn 't we have some people keep watch ?
You know , just in case something bad happens ?
( STUTTERS ) Who wants to stay out here ?
( SIGHS ) Fuck .
( DOOR CREAKING OPEN )
RICHIE : I can 't believe I pulled the short straw .
You guys are lucky you 're not measuring dicks .
EDDIE : Shut up , Richie .
I can smell it .
RICHIE : Don 't breathe through your mouth .
How come ?
Because then you 're eating it .
- ( EDDIE
GAGGING ) - ( UNZIPS FANNY PACK )
- (
INHALER HISSES ) - ( EDDIE
INHALING
SHARPLY )
What ?
It ... It says I 'm missing .
( STUTTERS ) You 're not missing , Richie .
RICHIE : " Police department , City of Derry . "
That 's my shirt . That 's my hair . That 's my face .
Calm down , this isn 't real .
That 's my name . That 's my age ! That 's the date !
It can 't be real , Richie .
No , it says it ! What the fuck ?
- Am I missing ? Am I gonna go missing ? - Calm down . Calm down .
Look at me , Richie . Look at me .
That ... That isn 't real .
It 's playing tricks on you .
GIRL : Hello ?
Hello ?
Help me , please !
( GIRL GASPING )
( RATS SQUEAKING )
( GIRL CHOKING )
( GIRL COUGHING )
( GASPS AND COUGHS )
Betty ?
Ripsom ?
- (
SCREAMS ) - ( ALL GASP )
( ALL BREATHING SHAKILY )
HOBO : Eddie ...
What are you looking for ?
Guys , can you hear that ?
( BREATHING RAGGEDLY )
RICHIE : She was just here . Where the fuck did she go ?
(
EXHALES
SHARPLY ) Guys .
- ( DOOR CREAKS OPEN ) - (
GROWLING )
EDDIE : (
GASPING ) Oh , my God .
Guys . Guys !
( DOOR SLAMS )
- Guys ! Guys ! - What ? Eddie ?
( SCREAMS ) What the fuck ?
( PANTING )
HOBO : Time to take your pill , Eddie .
( GROWLING )
( WHIMPERING )
( WATCH BEEPING )
( GROANS )
( DOOR JAMMING )
- Eddie . Open the door ! - BOY : Richie .
BILL : You okay ?
( BANGING ON DOOR ) Eddie , what 's going on ?
Eds .
Eddie .
BOY : Come here , Richie . ( LAUGHS )
Where the fuck are you ?
We 're not playing hide-and-seek , dipshit .
BILL : Richie ?
Richie ! Richie !
Bill , come on , open the door .
It won 't open !
- What 's going on ? Richie ! - I can 't !
- ( DOOR
JAMMING ) - BILL : Open the door , Rich .
( BREATHING RAGGEDLY )
RICHIE : Oh , shit .
( EERIE LAUGHTER )
( LAUGHTER CONTINUES )
( GASPS )
( SCREAMS )
( RICHIE GASPING )
( LIGHTS BUZZING )
Stupid clowns .
Oh , fuck .
( SQUELCHING )
Ugh !
- (
YELLING ) - (
SCREAMS )
Beep-beep , Richie .
- ( YELLS ) - (
SCREAMING )
Let 's get outta here .
( GRUNTS AND LAUGHTER )
You wanna play loogie ?
( RETCHING )
- (
DISTORTED
LAUGHTER ) - (
RATTLING )
( GASPS )
( PANTING )
( WINCES )
( TAPPING )
( HEAVY BREATHING )
- (
PENNYWISE
LAUGHING ) - (
WHIMPERING )
( GRUNTING )
( PENNYWISE LAUGHING )
Time to float .
( WHIMPERING )
( MOCK GASPING )
( CONTINUES GASPING )
( SCREAMS )
- (
EXCLAIMING ) - (
WHIMPERING AND
SOBBING )
( PENNYWISE LAUGHING )
- (
IMITATES
SOBBING ) - (
SOBBING )
BETTY : Where 's my shoe ?
( BOTH SCREAM )
Where the fuck were her legs ?
Holy shit , what the fuck was that ?
This isn 't real .
Remember the missing kid poster .
That wasn 't real , so this isn 't real .
- Tasty , tasty , beautiful fear . - (
WHIMPERING )
Come on . Ready ?
RICHIE : No !
EDDIE : No .
- (
GROWLING ) - (
WHIMPERING )
EDDIE : No , no !
Oh , thank fuck .
- BILL : Where 's Eddie ? - EDDIE : Help !
Help !
RICHIE : Eddie !
Holy fuck .
Eddie !
This isn 't real enough for you , Billy ?
I 'm not real enough for you ?
Oh , shit .
It was real enough for Georgie .
( PENNYWISE LAUGHS )
( ROARING )
- RICHIE : Holy shit ! - ( YELLS )
- ( GRUNTS ) - ( BOTH GASP )
( WAILING )
- Get Eddie ! - Get Eddie !
- ( EDDIE
SCREAMING ) - ( ALL
CLAMORING )
( GROWLS )
Oh , fuck ! We gotta get out of here !
( BOYS SCREAMING )
( DEEP GROWLING )
( ALL SCREAMING )
- BILL : Get Eddie . Let 's go ! - RICHIE : Guys , watch out !
- EDDIE : No , no , no , no ! - Eddie , look at me !
EDDIE : He 's gonna get us ! Guys !
No ! ( SCREAMS )
- (
SCREAMS ) - ( YELPS )
( LAUGHING )
- ( GROANS ) - BILL : Ben !
RICHIE : Ben !
- (
GRUNTING ) - ( KIDS
CLAMORING )
RICHIE : Let 's get out of here !
Don 't let him get away !
( ALL SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY )
BEVERLY : Bill , we have to help Eddie !
No ! No !
RICHIE : I 'm gonna snap your arm into place .
Rich , do not fucking touch me .
- Okay , one , two , three . - Do not touch me !
- ( BONES CRACK ) - (
SCREAMS )
- ( KIDS
CLAMORING ) - MIKE : Holy shit !
You . You did this .
You know how delicate he is .
- ( STUTTERS ) We were attacked , Mrs. K. - No . Don 't .
Don 't try and blame anyone else .
- Let me help . - Get back !
Oh , I 've heard of you , Miss Marsh .
And I don 't want a dirty girl like you touching my son .
Mrs. K , I ... (
STUTTERS )
No ! You are all monsters . All of you .
And Eddie is done with you . Do you hear ? Done !
( ENGINE STARTS )
I saw the well .
( STUTTERS ) We know where it is
and next time we 'll be better prepared .
No !
No next time , Bill .
- You 're insane . -
BEVERLY : Why ?
We all know no one else is going to do anything .
Eddie was nearly killed ! And look at this motherfucker .
He 's leaking Hamburger Helper !
BEVERLY : We can 't pretend it 's gonna go away .
Ben , you said it yourself , It comes back every 27 years .
Fine ! I 'll be 40 and far away from here .
I thought you said you wanted to get out of this town , too .
Because I wanna run towards something . Not away .
I 'm sorry , who invited Molly Ringwald into the group ?
- Richie ... - I 'm just saying , let 's face facts .
Real world .
Georgie is dead . Stop trying to get us killed , too .
Georgie 's not dead .
You couldn 't save him , but you can still save yourself .
( STUTTERS ) No , take it back .
You 're scared and we all are , but take it back !
BEVERLY : Bill !
RICHIE : You 're just a bunch of losers !
- Fuck off ! - STANLEY : Richie , stop .
You 're just a bunch of losers and you 'll get yourselves killed
- trying to catch a fucking stupid clown . - Stop !
This is what It wants .
It wants to divide us .
We were all together when we hurt It .
That 's why we 're still alive .
Yeah ? Well , I plan to keep it that way .
- Mike ... - Guys ...
I can 't do this .
My granddad was right .
I 'm an outsider . Gotta stay that way .
( MUSIC PLAYING )
( INAUDIBLE )
( FIRES GUN )
( GUNSHOT )
- Yeah ! Bonus ! - Yeah , there we go .
Put the next target out there .
( CAT MEOWS )
- Just hold it . - ( CAT
MEOWING )
What the hell 's going on here ?
Just cleaning your gun , like you asked .
You 're cleaning my gun , huh ?
- Dad ... - Hey !
- ( HENRY
WHIMPERING ) - Look at him now , boys .
Ain 't nothing like a little fear to make a paper man crumble .
( MUSIC PLAYING FAINTLY ON SPEAKERS )
KEENE : Here for the refills , Eddie ?
Yeah .
GRETTA : You know it 's all bullshit , right ?
What is ?
Your medication .
They 're placebos .
What 's placebo mean ?
Placebo means bullshit .
No friends , huh ?
Your cast .
No signatures or anything ?
So sad .
I didn 't want it to get dirty .
I 'll sign it for you .
VICTOR : You okay , Henry ?
( KIDS LAUGHING IN DISTANCE )
( LAUGHTER CONTINUES )
HOSTESS : ( ON TV ) And this is my most favorite part of the afternoon .
Getting to know all about so many of you .
Is there someone here that wants to share with us
- what they most enjoyed about today ? - GIRL : Me !
- HOSTESS : How about you ? - GIRL : I liked seeing the clown .
- HOSTESS : You did ? You liked the clown ? - KIDS : Yes !
- HOSTESS : What about the rest of you ? - BOY : I liked when the bubbles float .
HOSTESS : You did ? Me too .
I just love watching things float .
BOYS : We all float .
That 's right .
And you will , too , Henry .
Make it a wonderful day .
Kill him .
ALL : Kill him . Kill him .
Kill him . Kill him .
( KNIFE CLICKS )
ANNOUNCER : Oh , no . Give a big round of applause !
( OFFICER BOWERS GROANING )
( HENRY PANTING )
( GRUNTING )
HOSTESS : Well done , Henry .
Kill them all . Kill them all .
Kill them all !
Kill them all ! Kill them all ! Kill them all !
( CHANTING CONTINUES )
KIDS : Kill them all ! Kill them all ! Kill them all !
MR. MARSH : Where are you sneaking off to ?
( STAMMERS ) Nowhere , Daddy .
You 're looking prettied up .
I 'm not prettied up , Daddy . I wear this almost every day .
Come .
You know I worry about you , Bevvie .
I know .
People in town have been saying some things to me about you .
Sneaking around all summer long with a bunch of boys .
The only girl in the pack .
They 're just friends , I swear .
I know what 's in boys ' minds when they look at you , Bevvie .
I know all too well .
My hand ...
Are you doing womanly things down in the woods with those boys ?
No , no , no , nothing . You don 't have to worry . I promise .
What 's this ?
It 's nothing . It 's just a poem .
Just a poem ?
But you had to hide it in your underwear drawer .
Why would you have to hide it there ?
( BREATHING SHAKILY )
Are you still my girl ?
No .
MR. MARSH : What did you say ?
I said , no !
- ( GRUNTS ) - (
BEVERLY YELPS )
No !
Get away , no !
( SCREAMING )
Get off !
No !
( GASPING )
Those boys . Do they know that you 're my ...
- ( GRUNTS ) - ( GROANS )
( PANTING )
( DOORKNOB RATTLES )
( GRUNTS )
- ( YELLS ) - ( GRUNTS )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( GROANING SOFTLY )
BILL : Beverly ?
( GROANING )
( BREATHING SHAKILY )
Beverly !
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
- BILL : Richie . - What do you want ?
See that guy I 'm hitting ? I 'm pretending it 's you .
( STUTTERS ) It got Beverly .
What are you talking about ?
It , Richie .
It got Beverly .
( PHONE RINGING )
Hello ?
Okay .
( SIGHS )
I 'll meet you there .
( INDISTINCT CHATTER ON TV )
And just where do you think you 're off to ?
Out with my friends .
Sweetie , you can 't go .
You 're getting over your sickness , remember ?
My sickness ?
Okay , what sickness , Ma ?
You know what these are ? They 're gazebos !
They 're bullshit !
( PILLS CLATTERING )
They help you , Eddie .
I had to protect you .
Protect me ?
By lying to me ? By keeping me locked inside this hellhole ?
I 'm sorry but the only people that were
actually trying to protect me were my friends .
And you made me turn my back on them when I really needed them .
So I 'm going .
Eddie . Eddie . No .
You get back here .
- Sorry , Mom , I gotta go save my friends . - (
SOBBING ) Eddie !
Don 't do this to me , Eddie !
Guys , spikes .
( GRUNTS )
( RAT SQUEAKING )
( DOOR CREAKING )
BEN : Stan ?
Stan , we all have to go .
( STUTTERS ) Beverly was right .
If we split up like last time , that clown will kill us one by one .
But if we stick together ,
all of us ,
we 'll win .
I promise .
RICHIE : Hey , Eddie , you got a quarter ?
I wouldn 't want to make a wish in that fucking thing .
Beverly ? ( ECHOES )
MIKE : How are we supposed to get down there ?
All right . Come on .
( RATTLING )
All right .
( GRUNTS )
( BILL GRUNTING )
- (
STRAINING ) - ( METAL
CREAKING )
( WHISPERS ) Guys , guys . Help .
- RICHIE : All right , buddy ? - Yeah , I 'm okay .
( GRUNTING )
PENNYWISE : ( ON
SPEAKERS ) Step right up , Beverly . Step right up .
( MUSIC BOX PLAYING )
Come change . Come float . You 'll laugh . You 'll cry .
You 'll cheer . You 'll die .
Introducing Pennywise the Dancing Clown .
( LAUGHING MANIACALLY )
( MUSIC BOX CONTINUES PLAYING )
( MUSIC STOPS )
( LAUGHS )
( CIRCUS MUSIC PLAYING )
( MUSIC PLAYING DISTORTEDLY )
( PENNYWISE LAUGHING )
( STRUGGLING )
( CONTINUES LAUGHING )
I 'm not afraid of you .
( SNIFFS )
( GRUNTING )
You will be .
( BOY SCREAMING )
BOY : Help ! Help me !
( MIKE SIGHING )
( EXHALES )
- ( GRUNTS ) - Ahhh !
HENRY : Die !
BEN : Mike !
-
STANLEY : Mike ! - EDDIE : Mike !
STANLEY : You okay ? Mike !
RICHIE : Bowers .
Mike . Fuck .
( LAUGHS )
- BILL : Mike ! - BEN : Where is he ?
RICHIE : We 're next .
STANLEY : No , no , no !
- Grab it ! - EDDIE : Get the rope ! Get the rope !
Oh , shit .
- BILL : Mike ! - RICHIE : Mike !
Leave him alone !
You didn 't listen to what I told you , did you ?
You should 've stayed out of Derry .
Your parents didn 't and look what happened to them .
I still get sad every time I pass by that pile of ashes .
Sad ,
that I couldn 't have done it myself .
STANLEY : Run , Mike !
( BOTH GRUNTING )
ALL : Mike !
HENRY : Fuck down !
( STUTTERS ) I should get up there .
Are you insane ? With what ?
( COCKS GUN )
( GRUNTS )
( HENRY BREATHING HEAVILY )
( GASPS )
( GRUNTS )
( YELLING )
( HENRY YELLING )
RICHIE : Holy shit .
- BILL : Oh , my ... - EDDIE : Mike !
I 'm okay .
- ( ALL EXHALE ) - I 'm okay .
Shoot !
BEVERLY : Stanley .
STANLEY : Beverly ?
Is that you ?
( PENNYWISE LAUGHING )
( GASPING )
( METAL CLANGS )
Guys ?
- EDDIE : What ? - RICHIE : Guys , where 's Stan ?
EDDIE : Stanley !
Stanley !
Stan !
Oh , shit . Greywater .
Stan ?
BILL : Stan ?
EDDIE : Stanley !
( FOOTSTEPS )
( GASPS )
- (
FOOTSTEPS ) - ( GASPS )
( FOOTSTEPS RUNNING )
( SCREAMING )
( STANLEY SCREAMS )
- MIKE : Stan ! - RICHIE : Shit ! Stan !
EDDIE : Stanley !
- We 're coming , man ! - We 're coming ! Don 't worry .
( ALL STRAINING )
- BILL : Stan ? - EDDIE : Stanley ! Stan !
His flashlight !
( ALL GASP )
RICHIE : What the fuck is that thing ?
Oh , shit .
( EDDIE SCREAMS )
( ALL EXCLAIMING AND WHIMPERING )
RICHIE : Oh , shit .
( SCREAMS )
( BOYS SCREAM )
Oh , shit !
Stanley !
- BILL : Stanley ! Stan ! - EDDIE : Stanley !
(
SCREAMING ) No ! No ! No !
- ( ALL CLAMOR ) - BILL : It 's okay .
You left me ! You took me into Neibolt !
You 're not my friends !
You made me go into Neibolt !
- EDDIE : Stanley , I 'm sorry . - STANLEY : You made me go into Neibolt !
( OVERLAPPING CHATTER )
STANLEY : This is your fault .
EDDIE : We would never let anything happen to you .
We 're here for you .
BEN : You know we wouldn 't do that to you . Come on .
Bill ! Bill !
MIKE : Bill !
EDDIE : Bill !
( BILL PANTING )
( STATIC WARBLES )
Beverly !
( GRUNTS )
I 'll come back for you , Bev .
BEN : Bill !
Bill !
- ( EDDIE GAGS ) - RICHIE : Come on .
Get out of there , dude . That 's greywater .
Wait , wait , wait . Oh , my God , my fucking flashlight ?
- ( ALL GASP ) - RICHIE : Eddie !
( ALL SCREAMING )
RICHIE : Come on , let 's get the fuck out of here ! Come on !
- RICHIE : Holy shit . - MIKE : Bev ? Bev ?
- BEN : Beverly ? - RICHIE : Holy shit .
BEN : Bev .
RICHIE : How is she in the air ?
Guys .
Are those ...
STANLEY : The missing kids .
Floating .
- BEN : Just let me grab her . - RICHIE : Shit .
( GRUNTING )
BEN : I 'm slipping .
Bev .
Beverly .
( YELLING ) Why isn 't she waking up ?
What is wrong with her ?
Beverly , please ! Come on !
( ALL EXCLAIMING )
RICHIE : Wow .
( GASPS )
BEN : Bev ?
" January embers "
" My heart burns there too "
Jesus , fuck .
Oh , God .
Where 's Bill ?
BILL : Georgie .
GEORGIE : What took you so long ?
I was looking for you this whole time .
I couldn 't find my way outta here .
He said I could have my boat back , Billy .
( PANTS )
Was she fast ?
I couldn 't keep up with it .
" She , " Georgie .
You call boats " she . "
Take me home , Billy .
( TEARFULLY ) I wanna go home .
( SOBS )
GEORGIE : I miss you . I wanna be with Mom and Dad .
I want more than anything for you to be home .
With Mom and Dad .
BILL : I miss you so much .
( SNIFFLES )
I love you , Billy .
I love you , too .
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( CRYING )
But you 're not Georgie .
- ( FIRES GUN ) - ( BILL GASPS )
( GRUNTING )
( SCREAMING )
( DISTORTED ROARING )
( ROARING CONTINUES )
( ROARING STOPS )
( PENNYWISE GASPS )
- EDDIE : Kill It , Bill ! Kill It ! - RICHIE : Shit .
- RICHIE : Kill It , Bill ! - ( BOYS
SHOUTING )
- Kill It ! Bill , Kill It ! - ( EDDIE
SCREAMS )
- ( ALL
SHOUTING ) - EDDIE : Kill It !
- Kill It ! - Kill !
Kill It !
It 's not loaded .
RICHIE : Do it now , Bill ! Kill It ! Kill It !
Hey ! It 's not loaded !
- ( GUN FIRES ) - (
GRUNTING
MANIACALLY )
RICHIE : Holy fuck .
- (
PENNYWISE GRUNTS ) - RICHIE : Oh , shit .
ROARING ) - ( ALL GASP )
- ( ALL
YELPING ) - (
GROWLING )
RICHIE : Bill , watch out !
BEVERLY : Leave him alone !
- ( YELLS ) - ( GROWLS )
EDDIE : Beverly , no !
STANLEY : Mike !
( MIKE SCREAMS )
( GRUNTS )
BEVERLY : Help him !
- ( GRUNTS ) - RICHIE : Fuck !
( BEN GRUNTS )
EDDIE : Ben !
- ( GRUNTS ) - ( BEN YELLS )
- ( GRUNTS ) -
BEVERLY : Stanley !
( YELPS )
( BILL GRUNTS )
EDDIE AND
STANLEY : Bill !
- EDDIE : Bill ! - ( LOW
GROWLING )
BEVERLY : No , don 't .
Let him go .
No .
I 'll take him .
I 'll take all of you .
And I 'll feast on your flesh as I feed on your fear .
Or ,
you 'll just leave us be .
I will take him , only him
and then I will have my long rest
and you will all live to grow and thrive
and lead happy lives
until old age takes you back to the weeds .
( GROWLING SOFTLY )
Leave ...
I 'm the one who dragged you all into this .
(
STUTTERS ) I 'm so sorry .
PENNYWISE : (
IMITATES
STUTTER ) Sorry .
( PENNYWISE LAUGHS )
- Go ! - (
PENNYWISE LAUGHS )
Guys , we can 't !
BILL : (
STUTTERS ) I 'm sorry .
I told you , Bill .
I fucking told you .
I don 't want to die .
It 's your fault .
You punched me in the face .
You made me walk through shitty water .
You brought me to a fucking crackhead house .
And now ...
I 'm gonna have to kill this fucking clown .
Welcome to the Losers ' Club , asshole !
- (
ROARING ) - ( GRUNTS )
( GRUNTS )
( ALL SCREAM )
-
BEVERLY : Mike ! - Mike !
- ( MIKE
STRAINING ) - (
STANLEY GRUNTS )
( RICHIE GRUNTS )
BILL : Stan , watch out !
- (
STANLEY YELLS ) - ( YELLS )
EDDIE : Mike !
- (
PANTING ) - (
LAUGHING
MANIACALLY )
( PENNYWISE GASPS )
EDDIE : Kill him !
( BEN YELLS )
( GRUNTS )
( INDISTINCT SHOUTING )
( BEN GRUNTS )
( SCREAMING )
( ROARING )
( GASPING )
( BILL GRUNTS )
( RICHIE GRUNTS )
( ALL GRUNTING AND YELLING )
( COUGHING )
( WHIMPERING )
( GAGS )
I 'm gonna kill you !
- ( EDDIE GRUNTS ) - (
PENNYWISE GROWLS )
PENNYWISE : Hey , Bevvie . Are you still my little ...
- (
YELLING ) - (
SCREAMS )
( CHOKING )
- ( GRUNTS ) - EDDIE : Oh , shit !
( GRUNTING )
( GROANING )
( GRUNTING MANIACALLY )
( GASPING )
( CHUCKLING )
That 's why you didn 't kill Beverly .
( STUTTERS ) ' Cause she wasn 't afraid .
- And we aren 't either . - ( MOCK
STUTTERING )
Not anymore .
Now you 're the one who 's afraid .
Because you 're gonna starve .
( GURGLING )
( GRUNTS )
PENNYWISE : " He thrusts his fists against the posts
" and still insists he sees the ghosts
( STUTTERS ) " He thrusts his fists against the posts "
( STUTTERING )
( GRUNTS )
( LOW GROWLING )
Fear ...
I know what I 'm doing for my summer experience essay .
( SIGHS DEEPLY )
( BEVERLY SNIFFLES )
Guys . Guys .
The kids are floating down .
( RICHIE SIGHS )
( SOBBING )
( SNIFFLES )
( CONTINUES SOBBING )
BEVERLY : I can only remember parts ,
I thought I was dead .
That 's what it felt like .
I saw us , all of us together back in the cistern ,
but we were older ,
like , our parents ' ages .
( STUTTERS ) What were we all doing there ?
I just remember how we felt .
How scared we were .
I don 't think I can ever forget that .
Swear it .
Swear
if It isn 't dead ,
if It ever comes back , we 'll come back , too .
( EXHALES )
( WINCES )
( WATCH BEEPING )
STANLEY : I gotta go .
I hate you .
( ALL LAUGHING )
I 'll see you later .
BILL : Bye , Stan .
EDDIE : Bye , guys .
-
BEVERLY : Bye , Mike . - MIKE : See you later , losers .
- RICHIE : See you around , Bill . - BILL : See you , Rich .
BEN : See you guys later .
BEVERLY : Bye , Ben .
( STUTTERS ) You all packed for Portland ?
Yeah , pretty much .
I 'm going tomorrow morning .
How long will you be gone ?
My aunt , she says I can stay for as long as I want , so ...
Just so you know ...
I never felt like a loser when I was with all of you .
See you around .
Bye .
( PENNYWISE LAUGHING )
^ . ^ . ^ . ^ .COLORED by . ^ . ^ . ^ . ^ ® Sud _ Arun collections ®